

FAVOUR OSEMUDIAMEN ORUKPE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Highly experienced web developer that specializes in frontend development and frameworks such as React, GatsbyJS and NextJS. He is interested about building user-friendly, aesthetically pleasing websites that serve business needs. Favour adopts a collaborative style and takes pleasure in resolving challenging technical problems in order to create a final result that meets customer objectives.

Contact

+(234) 814-038-9939

Edo State, Nigeria

linkedin.com/in/favour-orukpe-31432725b

github.com/alphadevking

alphadevking@gmail.com

General Skills

HTML 5.0 80%

CSS 3.0

JAVASCRIPT

TYPESCRIPT 95%

BOOTSTRAP 5

PYTHON

GIT

90%

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

70%

Education

AMBROSE ALLI UNIVERSITY

November, 2018 - May, 2023

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science.

AISOTECH COMPUTERS

January - March 2022

Awesome student, Industrial Training in Computer Networking.

Experience

AISOTECH COMPUTERS

August 2022 - Present

Tutor, Front-end web development who specializes in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and frameworks such as Next.JS, GatsbyJS and Vite.

SMART EARNERS TEAM

September 2022 - Present

Intern with a passion for web development and expertise in React, Typescript, and Web3 technologies and blockchain integration.

Projects Done

A MINIMAL NFT MARKETPLACE

Tech Stack: HTML 5.0 CSS 3.0 JAVASCRIPT

NFTs are listed for sale.

BLOCKCHAIN-BASED SAFE

Tech Stack: TYPESCRIPT CSS 3.0 WEB 3.0

Cryptocurrency lock, safely stores your coins and assets.

NFT AND VR-AUGUMENTED INTERACTION

Tech Stack: TYPESCRIPT CSS 3.0 WEB 3.0

Connecting ur NFTs and Virtual Reality in a unique space, where you have full control over your assets - Buy, sell, exchange etcetera.